What's up, WORLD? IT'S YOUR BOY NATE
JACKSON. THIS IS A SUPER FUNNY COMEDY
JAM. WE TAPING LIVE IN TACOMA,
WASHINGTON. Let me introduce you to the
comics on this episode. There they
[screaming] go.
>> I'm Jackie Turges from right here in
Tacoma, Washington. [cheering]
>> Hey, I'm Fat Man Dy from Decada,
Georgia. Bro, [cheering]
last name Dashas. I represent VA
Northford to be exact.
>> [cheering]
>> I'm Dominique. I'm from the south side
of Washington DC. [cheering]
>> Hey [music] Jackson,
super funny jam. [music]
Super funny jam.
Jackson [music]
[singing] jam.
>> What's up y'all?
This is super funny comedy jam and it's
going down. Hey man, we tap it right
here live in Tacoma. I'm so proud of the
little city I'm from right here. This
[\h__\h] going down. Really? I'm from like
Lacy, Olympia, but [\h__\h] it. [cheering]
If this is any other city in the world,
all this [\h__\h] is the same.
Everybody smacking the same cheeks.
Should I start over? Did I just rub
y'all? I'm like, wait a minute, [\h__\h]
What did we do to him?
We in here though. Y'all got Y'all look
good. You got your little church shirt
on. Got a little I see what you're
doing. Okay. You fine as a [\h__\h]
Look like a little sexy rooster. Girl,
go ahead. Yeah. Yeah. Get some dick
doodle do in this [\h__\h]
Yeah. I see you in your fatigues and
[\h__\h] Tin hut. [\h__\h] you look good.
Yeah. Is there any couples in the
building?
[cheering]
>> [applause]
>> Let's be really honest. Is there anybody
in a relationship and you on your last
leg? Y'all not going to make it. Clap
one time. She clap in his face. If this
I can't I can't I can't. That's what's
up. Where the single women single?
[cheering]
>> Yeah. [screaming]
Yeah. Yeah. Sexy rooster.
Dang.
Some of the women sounded confident like
I ain't got nobody. Yay. Hey,
your house chirping like a [\h__\h]
[laughter]
You need a man and a ladder. Somebody
need to change them batteries out. Your
house is about to catch on fire and you
won't even know.
Bed cold.
Got to get in bed and warm it up with
your own legs. Ain't nobody in there.
[laughter]
Get in your bed every night and go like
this.
Whole garage on fire.
And there you go. Now I feel like I have
somebody.
I'm enjoying myself. [\h__\h] This is what
we going to do, man. We going to start
this episode up. We got some monsters on
this episode. If y'all ready to start
the show, start clapping right now.
IF YOU'RE READY TO START THE SHOW, START
CLAPPING RIGHT NOW. [cheering]
FIRST COMEDIAN COMING TO THE STAGE.
Y'ALL MAKE SOME NOISE FOR JACKIE TERESA.
[music]
TACOMA, how we feeling? [music]
>> Oh my god, I'm so happy to be here. I am
Jackie. I love telling people that I'm
like a stay-at-home mom cuz there's such
a stigma around house arrest.
Although, it turns out it's a lot easier
to be a present mother when it's court
order.
Oh my god, my kids love it. I'm like,
I'm here for you
for the next 8 to nine months, okay?
Depending on my behavior.
They're always like, "Don't go back to
the streets, Mom.
But I will." Okay. [cheering]
You can't keep me off them.
I've been having kids like crazy, too. I
had two kids in 18 months.
>> I know. This guy just grabbed his
uterus. Okay.
Same. Oh my god. Having kids destroyed
me. Okay. Like my stomach is just
confused after all the stretching, you
know. So, it reinvented itself as a
butt.
Little crack. Little crack and
everything. Oh my god. So cute,
sir. And uh then I did the right thing.
I bought mom jeans, right? You have to,
ladies. You got to tuck it in. You got
to give it a proper home.
I actually I call these my Tupperware
jeans
cuz it's where I put my baby leftovers.
[laughter]
Still fresh.
So good. I actually I had three kids.
Can we give it up for my pelvic floor?
[cheering]
[applause]
My god,
it needs the support if I'm going to be
real with you guys. Okay. Right. At this
point, it's less like a floor and more
like when you get a leak and the drywall
starts to sag.
Is that too graphic for you, sir?
[cheering] He's not making eye contact.
He's literally shielding his eyes. He's
looking around at his buddies. He's
like, "There's a FLOOR IN THERE, BRO.
DID YOU KNOW ABOUT THIS?" [laughter]
OH, DRYWALL. I know that, right? Drywall
a little bit. He said, "Listen, I just
sprinkle in construction words just to
say relatable to everybody." Okay.
Hammer,
right?
Monkey wrench.
[laughter]
What? What was your name, sir?
Chuck. That's such a nice name, Chuck.
Listen, I just pee a little bit all the
time now, Chuck. Okay. Like I've been
peeing this entire time. Okay.
Like I I used to have an in any right
here. Eye contact. I used
I used to have an Inie Aouty belly
button. Okay, Chuck. Now I have an Inie
cervix. Okay. Do you understand? OH,
GROW UP. IT'S IN right now. Okay.
[laughter]
Keeping that in. He's like, "Siri, what
is a cervix?" Uh,
which is fine. No, it's changed my life.
Like, I used to go to Pilates class. I
used to stay till the end. You know what
I mean? Remember those days? Now I'm
sneaking out halfway through. I'm
hobbled over like an old witch. I'm
like,
[laughter]
there's a lot more jumping in that class
than I remember. My shoes are squeaking.
I'm like,
>> [laughter]
>> THEY MUST have just washed the floor cuz
that's not my urine.
I do I do I just want to be a good mom,
you guys. And I would be if it weren't
for my kids.
I'd be the best, you know? I I do gentle
parenting.
Yeah. Nobody believes me cuz they heard
all the other [\h__\h] I said. Uh
>> [cheering]
>> No, I said gentle parenting in Idaho and
the whole crowd booed.
Like all of them booed. I was like,
"Okay, Boise, you guys just slapping
your kids left and right out here,
[laughter]
you know, mostly right.
It's a red state.
Not you guys. I can tell you'd never do
that. You'd only slap your kids left. I
like that about you.
Unless you're a libertarian, then I
guess they would slap themselves.
[laughter]
Oh, okay. He's like, "Siri, what is a
libertarian?" Uh, [laughter]
Philip Screwdriver.
Okay. I've been Jackie Turges. Thank you
guys so much. [cheering]
[music]
Baby, tell me
[applause]
[laughter]
[cheering]
asparagus.
She had me cracking up naming random
tools and she was like monkey rich. I'm
like [laughter]
that was a stripper move in a tool.
One more time, Jackie Teres, please.
[cheering]
More, more, more, more. Next comedian
coming to the stage. Hails from Decar,
Georgia. Y'all make some noise for Fat
[music]
Man.
>> [music]
>> Yeah. Hello.
>> I only got five minutes, bro. So, I
ain't f to ask y'all how y'all doing cuz
I don't have time for you to tell me.
Uh,
it had my bad time. Uh-huh. I done got a
little old, you know. I used to be
young. [clears throat]
You feel me? No, for real. I used to be
young. Used to want star [\h__\h] with
people, you You know, I remember when I
had got my first little pistol, you
know, and I put, you know, you put it
right here and put your shirt behind it.
You know what I'm saying? Cuz you want
people to know you got it. You feel me?
Cuz when I was young, you know, I used
to wish a [\h__\h] would, you know what I'm
saying?
And now I'm old, I just hope a [\h__\h]
don't,
you know what I'm saying? Like I got the
pistol, you feel me? I hope a [\h__\h]
don't do nothing, bro. Like I got the
strap, but I don't want to use it. You
feel me? Like, I don't want to shoot
nobody, bro. Like, the [\h__\h] It ain't
that, you know what I'm saying? Like, it
ain't that easy to kill no [\h__\h] bro.
Like, I I just don't believe that, bro.
I hit a squirrel, bro. The other day,
bro, and that [\h__\h] [\h__\h] me up, my
[\h__\h] I was like, god damn, bro. I
don't know why the [\h__\h] you know what
I'm saying? He ain't got damn but no jug
or nothing, bro. He just ran under the
tie. You know, your body get tight when
you f TO HIT THE [\h__\h] GOD DAMN
IT. YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN? [cheering]
I almost wrecked the clutch trying not
to hit this [\h__\h] squirrel, bro.
No, for real. My partner call me like,
"Come pick me up." Like, "Hell no,
[\h__\h] These squirrels out here
bullshitting, boy." You feel me? I can't
have that on my heart, my [\h__\h]
[laughter]
They drive for like 4 days, bro. You
know what I'm saying? And that was the
squirrels. I can only imagine a whole
[\h__\h] You feel me? Like,
just kill a [\h__\h] then go eat. You know
what I'm saying? Like, it don't work
like that. Anyway, you know what crazy,
bro? Like I I I I believe in God, you
know what I'm saying? I believe in
Jesus, you know, but like my black
friend now, they don't really want me
believe in Jesus. They want me to
believe in the ancestors. You know what
I'm saying? And like I ain't mad at the
ancestors. I just do the [\h__\h] that come
naturally to me. You know what I'm
saying? Like you have been driving your
car and you had slam on the brake cuz
you going to hit somebody. You throw
your arm out to protect somebody over
here. You know what I'm saying? And then
you just hit the brakes like Jesus. You
know what I'm saying? Like ain't nobody
taught me how to do that. I ain't have
to learn it at church. Nate. The first
time I ever slammed on the brake and
threw my arm out, I was like Jesus.
[\h__\h] it just came out. I ain't never
been driving and slammed on the brake
and been like ancestors. You know what
I'm saying? Like, hey, them [\h__\h] dead
as [\h__\h] baby. You feel me? Like, they
ain't they ain't coming, bro? I don't
know [laughter]
who the [\h__\h] on the way, but them [\h__\h]
ain't coming. You feel me?
Dead serious, man. Hey, I think that
like three minute right there.
No, I'm real. I got to count this [\h__\h]
cuz soon as it get good and they going
to be like, "Now I got to go." So, uh,
[laughter]
and like he said, I'm from Decada,
Georgia. You know what I'm saying? And
um,
y'all from there or something?
>> Oh, okay. No, I'm They making noise like
they from there, [\h__\h]
[laughter]
A [\h__\h] that from where I'm from can
describe every situation on earth with
three words. And them three words is
[\h__\h]
Goddamn.
You know what I mean?
Look, look. I'mma break it down for you.
I was talking to my partner and I
walking over here. He was like, "D
what's him?" I like ain't nothing. He
like, "But what you about to do?" I like
walk in this little super funny comedy
club right quick
and [\h__\h]
Goddamn,
you know what I mean?
That [\h__\h] was like, "Hell yeah, boy.
Come when we get through with that [\h__\h]
I'm be over in the hood cool." And I'm
like, "Okay,
what's up?"
That [\h__\h] work with the police, too.
Then one time I got pulled over. I
forgot my license at the house. police
come to the window. He like, "How you
doing, sir? You got your license on your
seat?" And I was like, "Shit.
God damn."
You know what I mean?
That [\h__\h] said, "Yes, sir. Go ahead and
step out the car for me. Serve me."
But
[laughter]
I think I seen the light.
But [\h__\h]
[laughter]
God damn.
Hey, [\h__\h] you talking about man. My name
fat man dies, bro. I appreciate that.
[music]
Fat man.
I was like, why are you so worried about
the time [clears throat]
[\h__\h]
Ah, damn.
I mean,
[laughter]
I'm not even from there. When I do that,
that might just be all black people, DC.
[laughter]
Women like, "Did you just bust?" I'm
like, "Shit."
God damn.
You know what I mean?
[laughter]
This [\h__\h] funny about
He's still doing it.
That was a Asian girl. [\h__\h] GOD DAMN
IT. [\h__\h] MEAN [\h__\h] THE GODDAMN IT.
Mother mean me.
[\h__\h] the god damn it.
Know what I mean?
[laughter]
I saw you Asian girl.
Shut the god damn it.
>> One more time. That fat man Dyes man.
[\h__\h] hilarious.
Hilarious.
Make some [\h__\h] noise [cheering]
for the next comedian coming to the
stage all the way from VA. [cheering]
[music]
>> What's happen? How y'all doing? Y'all
good?
>> Like it here, man. Y'all got a nice ass
town.
Y'all homeless people. Aggressive as
[\h__\h]
So I stopped at stoplight. The [\h__\h] got
in the car. So he
sat down, put his seat belt on,
pulled out his charger.
Unplugged my phone, plugged his [\h__\h] up.
Run me up the road, fam. [laughter]
I took him where he wanted to go. [\h__\h]
I ain't no killer. I gave up my life for
crime. [\h__\h] I was a thug, too. [\h__\h] I
ain't I'm still the most thug [\h__\h] in
Whole Foods.
Where I scared my white folks at? Hey,
[\h__\h] where the flax seed oil at?
[\h__\h] needs some collagen. Chop chop.
You ever seen the old thug? It's the
saddest [\h__\h] [\h__\h] They got a neck
full of jewelry, no health insurance,
[\h__\h] It's like, [\h__\h] you can't
afford to die. You walking around here
[\h__\h] with people. You
got time to be [\h__\h] You got a fail.
Ain't nobody scared of you.
Can't whip nobody ass. Your heart
skipping a beat. Gave that [\h__\h] I ain't
with all that smoke. I got compression
socks now. [\h__\h] I'm trying to trying to
stop this gal from coming on, [\h__\h] I
got grown ass man problem. [\h__\h]
Varicose veins and [\h__\h] Let's discuss
some real Look, I'm at that age where
the TV be singing my medication to me.
All that [\h__\h] sound the same, don't it?
You ever look at them commercials, you
like, "Man, I think I might got that."
Yeah, [\h__\h] I sneezed this morning and
a little [\h__\h] came out. I thought that
was normal.
Do you have nausea, heartburn,
indigestion, upset stomach?
They be lit on that goddamn commercial.
They make they make diarrhea look worth
almost getting. [\h__\h]
I want a hot pink suit.
Ain't nothing fun about diarrhea. [\h__\h]
I'm peeing out my ass. This [\h__\h] is
excruciating.
[\h__\h] horrible.
Hey man, you get older. Your check
engine light. Come on.
I [\h__\h] around back in August. I had a
terrible scare. Like I got hemorrhoids.
Yeah, this [\h__\h] [\h__\h] me up. I ain't
know what was wrong. I just know
something won't right with my ass when I
woke up. Yeah, I woke up. My [\h__\h] was
itching and burning.
It's like, [\h__\h] this window open. I I
know ain't no [\h__\h] crawling in the
window and violate me when I was sleep.
God damn, man.
My [\h__\h] was [\h__\h] man. My [\h__\h] was on
fire. [laughter]
It felt like a [\h__\h] was walking behind
me with a lit match right in my ass.
[laughter]
And I wanted to check, but I'm a man.
[\h__\h] I ain't Yeah. Yeah, I ain't going
to spread my cheeks in the mirror. Like,
[\h__\h] I I look I was like, you know
what? I I'mma let this [\h__\h] fester,
[\h__\h] I'm [laughter]
I suffer for three and a half days,
[\h__\h]
I I woke up one morning. I was like,
this [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I scooch to the edge
of the bed with a mirror. I was Yeah, I
got to go to the doctor. This [\h__\h] ain't
supposed to look like [laughter] this,
[\h__\h] My [\h__\h] was turned inside out.
That's what he turn your [\h__\h] inside
out.
I went to the doctor. I was like, "Doc,
please tell me I ain't got ass cancer."
Like, I was scared to death. I'm a
comedian. I don't need that headline.
He's like, "Relax. You got hemorrhoids."
Like, I saw that commercial.
Give me my cream so I can get the [\h__\h]
out of here. [laughter] He was like,
"No, you need some suppositories."
I said, "What's that?"
gave me that nervous, you know, that the
nervous white man on the elevator smile.
We all done seen it. It [laughter]
[cheering]
We've all seen that [\h__\h] He They always
be on the balls of their feet.
[\h__\h] showed them to me. I was like,
"What? I'm supposed to chew them
[\h__\h] or something?" I was
[applause]
[laughter]
like, "Come on, dog. You ain't got no
gum or no [\h__\h] or a shake or something I
can drink."
Think I took them 45 caliber bullets of
wax home.
Hey man, that [\h__\h] Look, I ain't never
put nothing in my ass. Not even out of
curiosity.
And yet there I was,
naked as a [\h__\h] bent over the
sink with a tear coming out my eye.
But my ass stood in solidarity with me
cuz Yeah. He spit that [\h__\h] out about 15
times, [\h__\h] I kept ping my ass like,
"No, sir. [\h__\h] you ain't crossing
over, is you? You too old to be going to
the other team now. I kept trying to
stick it in. I kept trying to pick that
[\h__\h] up. I think I said [laughter]
I finally gave it a hunch.
Then my ass was oily and leaking. [\h__\h]
I don't even know why I'm telling y'all
this.
I just been doing this [\h__\h] for so long.
I just need an outlet. I need to relate
to some goddamn body.
[cheering]
Yeah, man. Look, [applause] I ain't no
thug no more. I got Wu Tang in my heart,
but [\h__\h] I got Frankie Beverly in my
knees and my back, [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] up. I used to like [\h__\h]
with older women. Now that I'm older,
they too [\h__\h] old.
Them conversation done changed. How you
doing today, Miss Pauline?
Well, baby, I ain't had a bowel movement
since Tuesday. It's like, god damn, that
ain't what I wanted to hear. Yeah,
that's that's penis repellent. Damn,
Miss Pauline. I
Yeah, but I'm at the age the young girl
be coming at me hard. Yeah, my
daughter's friend Kendra, that's your
daddy. I'm like, [\h__\h] you better get
your friend.
You going to [\h__\h] around and have sister
girlfriend walk around this [\h__\h] You
your father's still a bad man. I'll tear
her tender ass up.
I'm about to make y'all relationship
awkward as [\h__\h] [laughter] She called
me Zatty again. This a wrap.
I don't know what Zaddy mean, but that
[\h__\h] make my dick hard.
Hey, [\h__\h] that. I'm vulnerable.
>> Hey, I I can't do that [\h__\h]
Take no young girl out of here. You
ain't going to sit across from me and
ball your face up cuz you can't
pronounce the [\h__\h] I'm eating.
[laughter]
What's that, [\h__\h] It's quinoa.
No, not quinoa. You know what? You just
shut the [\h__\h] up and be cute and I'll
order for both of us.
My steak come to the table sizzling. She
over here arguing with the waitress cuz
she ain't bring her no honey mustard for
her chicken tenders. I'm just like, you
know what? Bring me my check. This [\h__\h]
ain't working out. Can you bring this
[\h__\h] her coloring book? Cuz I don't
know whether I'm [\h__\h] a babysitter.
[cheering] This This [\h__\h] is confusing.
Thank you very much y'all. Y'all have a
good night. I'm comedian Bation.
[cheering]
[music]
That [\h__\h] said, "I don't even know why
I'm telling y'all this.
My ass was oily and dripping.
This is disgusting.
We got uterus floor pee.
Booty pills. [laughter] I didn't even
know what he said was possible.
I don't know what year that kick in, but
I I So soon. Hold up.
I don't want no inside out ass now. I
want my ass outside in.
That's hilarious, man. Bacious
[\h__\h] hilarious. Y'all clap it
up for Bodacious one more time.
[cheering]
Yes, sir.
All right. Next comment coming to the
stage. Start make some noise right now.
Next comment coming to the stage. Make
some noise right now for the very funny.
[screaming]
[music]
How y'all doing,
man? When you old school, this lady is
[\h__\h] right now.
I be sleep. The old school people know
they been in here ning the whole goddamn
They nawing like they riding the bus.
That was funny. [laughter]
Ain't nothing wrong with being old
though. You got to keep up with your
health though. You really do. You got to
go to doctor. I went to a new doctor. He
came in the exam room and his ass was
fat. I said, "No,
I ain't going to no fat doctors."
I was like, "Excuse me, sir. I got to
leave." He said, "Well, why you
leaving?" I said, "Cuz we struggling
with the same [\h__\h]
Your fat ass can't read my chart. Are
you kidding me?
I know my A1C better than yours.
I've been walking and drinking water.
You know what I mean? [cheering]
Can't read my A1C. I said, you be eating
M&M's at night, too, fat boy.
Fat boy.
You can't listen to my heartbeat. That's
your [\h__\h] thumping. You can't listen to
me. had me going to cardiologist all
over the country and ain't nothing
wrong. [laughter] I said, "And change
the picture on your website, too.
That's your medical school picture.
Put that fat boy up and see what
happened. [cheering]
His name all the way under his arm. You
can't read my chart." [laughter]
You do though. You got to take care of
yourself. I think women do a better job
of it than men. We'll go to the doctor
quicker. It take men longer. It take a
lot of men longer. You know, by the time
they go, they be half dead already.
Yeah. They be doing home remedies and
[\h__\h] like that. No, it ain't going to
work. Cayenne pepper and patron. That
ain't about to work.
That ain't about to fix nothing.
[laughter] Then when it get real bad,
that's when they got to tell you. But
when they tell you it be something
weird, you know what I mean? They be
like, "You know I've been bleeding."
What you mean YOU BEEN BLEEDING?
WHAT you mean?
You need to go to the emergency room.
You think they going to keep me? Yeah,
THEY GOING TO KEEP YOUR EYES.
You bleeding. You should have went in
when you was spotting. You bleeding.
You behind the curve. You know what I'm
saying?
They going to run a battery of test on
your ass. You in bad shape when they
tell you they going to run a battery of
test on. [laughter]
It's a lot of young people in here too.
It's old school people. This young
people young people think old school
people talk about them bad. And I say we
will but it's we do but it's just a
difference of generation.
It's different. Like even the way young
people steal it's different. [laughter]
Like when I was growing up, we had
boosters,
>> you know? They would wear tights and
they tried to be discreet. Not the new
generation. They get a group of friends
and run up there and rob your [\h__\h]
Damn.
They don't care. They still just flat
out in front of everybody.
So I I was at the store and I was at the
register checking out. So I could see
the dude over there stealing. I was
watching him, but I he he was it was
weird because he was complaining like
they don't had extra large. [laughter]
I said that ain't how you steal.
I thought you just take it and leave.
You know what I'm saying? [cheering]
So, I'm at the register. So, I asked the
cashier. I said, "You don't see him
stealing?" "Yeah, I see him." I said,
"Well, you're not going to say nothing."
They told us not to say nothing. I said,
"Well, give me my goddamn credit card
back then."
And I'm going to take this [\h__\h] and
don't you say nothing.
Simple ass self. [cheering]
Simple ass self. And he going to slide
it to me. I said, "Put it in the bag.
I ain't about to walk out here like I'm
stealing. What is wrong with you?
These young people crazy.
They different,
but they all right. They just growing
up. Any school teachers here?
>> Yeah.
>> All right.
>> Right there back there.
>> Sixth grade.
>> Sixth grade. Okay. She scared me for a
minute. I said, "Where's she at?"
All I heard was, "Yeah,
but I commend school teachers because I
think school teachers need to make more
money."
They [cheering] do.
[applause]
Yeah, they do. You don't want nobody
that's underpaid teaching your baby.
>> Mess your baby up on purpose. You know
what I'm [laughter] saying? They be in
there all day looking at power. You know
what I'm saying? Your baby get home, he
looking at power. [laughter] But in 2020
during the pandemic, them teachers
wasn't teaching nothing.
>> No. I realized that when my niece said
she made the honor roll. I said, "No,
you in 12th grade, you ain't never made
the honor roll. Now school at home.
You got all A's." [laughter]
I went in her room one time. She had her
head on the desk. I was like, "Well,
what you doing?" You know, we having
quiet time.
Not in 12th grade.
[cheering and applause] The teacher had
her head on the desk, too.
She was like, "We're having quiet time."
[laughter]
I said, "She tired." And she been binge
watching Netflix all night cuz Netflix,
Hulu, and all that stuff without no
commercials and stuff, that stuff will
kill you. It'll bust your brain wide
off. You don't you don't even realize
you in there numb on the right side of
your face. You in there got one I
talking about I'mma watch one more
episode.
Oh this [\h__\h] good. I'mma watch one more
episode
then you fall asleep and wake up and
rewind it. Now I'mma watch this episode.
Y'all ain't about to do me like that.
And Netflix they really got beside they
self. You wake up and they asking, "ARE
YOU STILL WATCHING IT?"
Don't ask me about I'm paying for this.
Yeah, I'm watching. Even if it's
watching me,
this stuff will kill you. It will.
But one thing about that pandmic, them
parents learned a different respect for
them teachers. When they had them kids
at home with them all that time, they
had a different respect cuz they had to
realize they baby wasn't bright as they
thought they was.
When he in there all day long with you
rocking and [\h__\h] and you in there trying
to be the teacher talking about, "Look
at the computer." [laughter] Uh-uh. Look
at the computer. Don't look at me. Look
at the computer. Do you hear what I'm
saying? Look at the computer.
Turn your head and look at the computer.
You're like, "Oh my god, I see why the
teacher keep calling me at work.
This [\h__\h] ridiculous. I'm about to call
myself at work.
Look at the computer."
And the teacher looking at you saying,
"Miss Smith, that's all I was trying to
say. Something the [\h__\h] wrong with
Dante.
I told you he was in here rocking. You
wanted to fight me. You know what I'm
saying?
Boy a little slow.
I just keep passing him. No child left
behind.
Can he read? Nope. But he ain't left
I graduating. Yes, you are. Keep on.
You got to have fun, too. And enjoy your
life.
You don't give but one. You might as
well have a good time.
>> Yeah. You ain't going to be here
forever.
I don't want to live too long though.
Like I want long life, but I don't need
it to be too long. [laughter]
>> Yeah. I don't want to be 112 and all
that. If I live to be that old, I'm
going to be asking God, "What lessons
have I not learned
that I'm still stuck here?"
You know what I mean? And I mean, like
my grandson's 76 years old.
I ain't ate solid food in 50 years.
Really? [laughter]
It's the worst. All your friends dead
already.
My grandfather though, he live to be a
hundra and he wasn't he did it was good,
but he wasn't happy with it. I was like,
"Pop this a blessing." He said, "No,
this some bullshit."
And sometimes he'll just practice dying.
You know what I'm saying? You look at
him, he like I'm going in a hole.
I'm Dominique. God bless you, ladies and
gentlemen. [cheering]
[music]
One more time for Dominique. Y'all
keep it going for all my comments.
Dominique Bodacious, Jackie Terson, Fat
Man Dy. Listen, that's our episode,
y'all. Appreciate y'all for watching.
This is the Super Funny [music] Comedy
Channel. Peace.
[music]